IN THE FOOD CHAIN
[Corne over call]
The final match of the UFS Fight Club
took place at
the old market site last night.
- [grunts]
- Care to guess the winner?
That female rabbit again, I assume?
Yes, name of Kyuu.
She's won 17 fights in a row.
[chuckles] It's getting harder
to bet against her.
[Yahya strains] Yeah, if she can survive
in the Black Market,
she's no ordinary herbivore.
How long has it been since you liberated
the live bait market?
Ten years? Something like that?
It's not like she's stuck there.
So why would Gohin make her an apprentice?
How would I know
the workings of a panda's mind?
I don't know,
but I think this will interest you.
Reports say he has one more apprentice.
Apparently, it's our rogue gray wolf.
Huh? Is that so?
The wolf again. Now, that is interesting.
Our final piece of intel
is on the ivory trafficking case.
We received an anonymous tip.
They sent this photo to us.
Here, take a look.
[strains]
They only took the tusks.
Hmm. Zoom in on that pipe to the right.
[digital zooming sound]
A 10K gate valve... in yellow?
[strains] I think those were
the valves installed
during the redevelopment of Center Street.
- Look into it.
- You got it.
Once you find it, I'll make my move.
[door opens]
- [Els] Legoshi?
- Hmm?
- Oh, my gosh! How are ya?
- I'm okay.
You guys having
a Festival of the Meteor meeting?
Yeah. [sighs] For all the good it's doing.
You've heard, right?
- Separate education split the club in two.
- [Legoshi] Hmm.
So we still haven't come up with
a festival plan.
But if we don't,
we were told they might move it
to some other high school
entirely this year.
I see. Even club activities are in danger.
Why'd you even have to bring it up?
Quite the predicament.
Yeah, we got to do something
before they screw us.
Well, I got to go now.
My boyfriend is waiting for me.
Uh... I... [splutters] Uh, yeah, sure.
- Bye, guys!
- Later.
So, you wanted advice?
[both grunting]
[Legoshi] This is an advice?
[straining] Well, if I said
I needed manual labor,
you wouldn't have shown up, would you?
Why didn't you ask Aoba or Tao?
[groans] Oh, quit whining!
I tried, but they weren't available.
So, what about the herbivores?
I'm sure they would've helped
if you asked 'em.
Yeah, I know.
But, to be honest...
I don't know.
I just feel more at ease
with other carnivores, I guess.
Everyone acts like
it's all the carnivores' fault
that we have separate education now.
It's not like we chose
to be born as carnivores.
Like, come on, give me a freakin' break!
[both strain]
- I mean... [pants]
- Huh?
In spite of all that, I do still love
those little leaf-eaters.
[sighs]
So, hey, what were you thinking,
dropping out of school?
If you were still here,
I'd have a better idea of how not to act.
Watching you fumble worse than me
was always educational.
[Legoshi] Okay, that was a bit rude.
I guess he is still growing up.
[rattling]
[Fudge sighs] So, uh...
Should we even bother with these
if we might not do the festival at all?
Good question.
[inhales deeply] Hey!
Is that Legoshi?
Oh, hey! Great to see you!
What are you doing here?
This mutt may have quit school,
but he never quit the drama club.
What? What is that supposed to mean?
Ah! Hey, Legoshi!
What? Long time no see!
What's this for?
We're going to build
a classroom partition, baby!
Yeah, good idea!
Duh, that's so simple!
We can just split the clubroom
down the middle, right?
Do you think the teachers
are going to be okay with that?
They're not going to have
much of a choice.
You know, now with the festival
on the line.
What? Why, did something happen
at the meeting?
Hey, what do you say
we get this stuff inside?
Uh, sorry. I actually have to
get to work now.
I'll be rooting for you.
I mean that, Bill.
[exclaims, stutters] Don't get all gushy!
- Best of luck, guys.
- Come visit again!
Dude has a job now?
- I wonder what kind of job.
- [Zoe] Hmm.
[Kai] Probably not customer service.
[train chugging past]
[Louis] The raw stink of the Black Market.
Disgusting.
But, it puts my heart at ease.
[inhales deeply] Pathetic.
I wonder what Ibuki would say
if he saw me being so... indecisive.
[bicycle wheels squeal]
- [Legoshi] Hey, Louis!
- Hmm?
Legoshi, hey.
- Look at you, all dressed up.
- [laughs] Yeah, I'm delivering udon.
So-- Uh... [hesitates]
Ah, this thing? [strains softly]
Nice, huh? And this one can't get eaten.
- [gasps, shudders]
- I'm just messing with you.
You don't need to look quite so mortified.
Sorry.
So, what, uh... I mean,
you're in university now, yeah?
Unlike you, I have many obligations.
Hmm? Those aren't fresh scars
on your face, are they?
- [chuckles nervously]
- What a dangerous delivery guy.
No, no, no, I'm not.
You haven't changed at all, have you?
Not one bit.
[Legoshi] And it hits me again.
Why are all the herbivore species
such beautiful, elegant creatures?
If it meant I could live alongside them,
and protect them,
I truly believe that I would be willing
to sacrifice anything.
Hey, Louis.
I think... I think
I just realized something awful.
[Louis] Hmm?
Up until now, I thought
I was driven by my own sense of honor,
taking on the injustices of life,
because that's
a carnivore's responsibility.
But that's not the case.
Turns out,
it's my disposition as a wolf
and my ridiculous fetishes.
I'm just a rampaging pervert.
None of it was for honor or justice.
Well, it took you long enough to realize,
you damn dog.
Huh?
Everybody else already knows
you're just a perverted wolf.
The reason you fell in love with Haru,
is because she was the first herbivore
to ever show you any attention
as a woman, isn't it?
Frankly, that's what all men are like.
And that disposition is also
part of who you are.
But regardless of being a pervert,
if there's something you can protect,
then I would call that justice.
Wow, Louis.
If you understand me,
then quit moping, pervert!
- [chuckles nervously]
- Chin up!
- [all groaning]
- To the right.
- Are you sure?
- Seriously?
[Dolph] How do you know
this is the right way?
[Agata] Yeah, the moon is in
the same direction as before.
Just look. The esteemed whiskers
point this way.
[Agata] Is there anyone here
who didn't pluck a whisker?
[Free sighs] Seeing the moon like this
always makes me think
of launching that attack with Louis.
[Victor] I wonder how he's doing.
For a deer, he was always more of a lion
than any of us were.
[chuckles] Yeah.
The current boss did get the Shishi-Gumi
back on its feet in no time,
but it's just not the same
as it used to be.
- [yelps]
- [Dolph] What is it?
- Shit! I stepped in poop!
- [all exclaim in disgust]
- Don't touch me!
- [Jimma groans] Just my luck.
We're turning left.
[amusing music playing]
[Victor] Anyway,
Kines has our group thriving.
Those young folks who got hooked
are coming to the Black Market
looking for raw meat in such numbers
that people are thanking us
for driving business.
Can't argue with results.
- [Dolph scoffs]
- [growls] Watch your mouth!
Look, here's the thing.
We lions are supposed to be dignified
with nobility and firm principles.
And it's like all of that is just gone.
Look at the way he treats his kills.
He doesn't think of those animals
as anything but food.
And the way he eats it
looks so unappetizing.
Yeah, that guy has
no meat consumption manners at all.
Ha, well, you're one to talk.
What do you think Ibuki would say
if he was alive?
Probably just to focus on the next job,
which I feel pretty good about.
The boss mentioned
a Masquerade Night Party,
but what do we do?
Oh, you know. We'll put on a little mask...
[laughs] ...and when no one knows
who we are, we can... [laughs wickedly]
Take out the competition
with a Kines or two, huh?
Sounds more to me like
they'll unveil some new drug.
Either way, we need to hurry
and get out of here.
We got to talk to this Deshico guy.
Otherwise, risk losing an arm or two... Huh?
It's the exit.
Feline intuition really ain't something
to doubt, huh?
- Huh?
[squeaking]
[dramatic classical music playing]
[Deshico] You completed the maze
in a mere three hours.
Well done, Shishi-Gumi.
Don't ever underestimate
the psychic power of our whiskers.
[Deshico] The feline family is said
to be filled with mystique, yes,
but lions, tigers, wildcats, jaguars...
it's laughable that
they could be considered mystical.
They're all far too clumsy.
- [Free] The hell?
- [Deshico] Gentle.
Having been called a spiritual cat myself,
that is simply my opinion,
as Deshico the civet.
[Free] You're just a kid!
Oh, please,
drink your coffee while it's hot.
[all groan softly]
[all sniffing]
[Deshico] Allow me to educate you
on the mystique of the civet.
The coffee beans carefully selected
and eaten by civets are called kopi luwak,
and brew a precious cup of coffee.
In fact, the very coffee you're drinking
was brewed with beans I ate
and later extracted from my excrement.
[all gasp]
You mean it's your... [stammer]
Yes. My poop.
[all gagging]
[chuckles] And the civet's
remarkable nature doesn't stop there.
We also have secretions
from our anal glands,
which are often coveted
as a raw material for perfumes.
Why are these abilities concentrated
solely around our bottoms, I wonder?
I used to agonize over it.
But when things pass through my body,
they transform into something
more beautiful and valuable.
So, now, I'm quite proud
of the creature I am.
[strained growling]
[laughing wickedly]
It's taking effect.
[strained growling]
Coffee is composed of about 98% water,
and the remaining 2% is from the beans.
Only these,
have skeletomuscular narcotic effects
similar to, or even greater than Kines.
So, this is what the boss is after?
This Hyperdrug is comprised of ivory,
little bits of animal flesh and bone...
[bats squeaking]
...all the blood these littles ones gather,
and some of and my kopi luwak.
You blend those all together to create
this perfect black gem, Melda.
[all] Melda?
Also called "deer dung."
It's more potent than anything else
that's been on the market before.
I've already lined up a buyer
for the first batch of these.
And that, of course, would be your boss.
That's what he plans to reveal
at the masquerade. It must be!
[all] Huh?
[music intensifies]
[sniffs]
Ah, that's nice! [chuckles]
Why, thank you. That's a bag of my poop.
- [all exclaiming]
- Cooties! Cooties!
That maze you came through
is made of coffee trees,
and there's a lot of poop in there.
I want you to collect it and return it
to me by the end of the night.
And why should we have to do that?
Yeah, the king of beasts doesn't
go around picking up shit!
Well, I told Melon
I could only produce the drug
if there was someone here to help me.
He didn't say?
[growls] Damn him!
- We're leaving.
- [growls]
Mmm. [inhales]
I wonder if Madara-Gumi or Inari-Gumi
would be interested then.
[all growling]
[music crescendos]
Damn it! Everyone, pluck a whisker!
- [horn honks]
- [engines whirring]
[Legoshi reading] "Legoshi the gray wolf,
we are grateful for your cooperation
in the crackdown on carnivore criminals.
I'd like to take this opportunity
to hear about the state of the city
from you, a brave citizen.
I'm inviting you to dinner, Yahya."
Uh... Here.
What's this?
YAHYA
Oh!
Oh, so sorry to keep you waiting, sir.
[mysterious music playing]
[Legoshi] Just what kind of beast
is Yahya?
What species?
Is he a carnivore? An herbivore?
[elevator dings]
Hmm.
Whoa! [laughs]
Whoa!
[panting]
[chuckles]
Wow! So cool!
That's the Baraena River.
And that must be the Custos Bridge.
[gasps] Hey, there's my apartment!
Wow, it looks so small from up here.
Whoa!
- [Yahya] The city is beautiful at night.
- Huh?
Come on in, Legoshi.
Huh.
Nice to meet you. So are you Mr. Yahya?
Sorry to call you all the way out here.
I hope they were
at least polite to you downstairs.
Yes, they were.
For dinner this evening,
I thought I'd treat you
to the special carrots we grow up here.
Though, perhaps, this cuisine doesn't
appeal to your taste, being a wolf.
It's perfect. Thank you very much.
But, uh...
You're Mr. Yahya,
as in the Beastar, right?
Hmm, why do you ask?
Ah, excuse me.
That was speculation on my part.
You have your own room on the top floor
of the police headquarters.
It's like you're overseeing them,
but mostly...
- these carrots are incredibly delicious!
- [Yahya] Hmm?
They're so sweet
with a hint of earthiness.
Oh, and the flesh is plump and chewy,
and the more you chew...
um, how do I put this?
I don't know, but I've never had
a carrot like this before.
And if you eat such great meals
all the time,
then you must be
a pretty important person.
You know, I... [chuckles]
So, I guess I just figured that...
- I'm sorry.
- Hmm? [laughs]
That's all right. I'm glad you like it.
Yes, the carrots that are grown here
are certainly special.
Managed with
the right water and nutrients,
and kept at the perfect humidity
and temperature at all times.
Only by maintaining a perfect environment
can something perfect can be born.
I think society ought to be the same.
Don't you agree?
[Legoshi] That's settles it.
He hasn't affirmed it,
but Mr. Yahya is probably the Beastar.
But if he is,
I wonder how much responsibility
rests on those towering shoulders.
Before we have dessert,
I'd like to show you something.
[tense music playing]
Understand I'm willing to accept
whatever hardship
or sacrifice is necessary
for the realization of a perfect society.
- Legoshi.
- Mmm?
Tell me, what do you think
the Beastar truly is?
Uh...
I think that...
both herbivores and carnivores
all have their own separate struggles,
but the reason they're able
to still live happily,
is because of the hope that the Beastar
represents to everyone.
So, we... we all try to live up
to this ideal that exists within us.
Or something like that. Yeah.
That's an interesting approach.
However, I'd say the Beastar
is a much more realistic entity.
It's not hope.
A Beastar, you see, exacts law and order.
Law and order?
I mean, I... I actually kind of like seeing
some of the imperfections of our society.
But the fact that
it functions despite them,
is all thanks to you, isn't it?
That's amazing.
[Yahya] What a polite,
agreeable young wolf he is.
Almost carefree.
This kid gets on my nerves.
But I'm sure you've wondered.
So, let me ask you directly.
Do you not find it strange
that one horse alone
has the strength to battle
the evils of the world?
So, what, do you work out or something?
[scoffs] I do. But I still require
an additional source of energy.
[Legoshi] Hmm.
When you become a Beastar,
you have one wish granted,
no matter what it may be.
Even, for instance,
if you want to turn the carnivores
you've punished
into fertilizer for your garden,
that's perfectly acceptable.
And with your previous record
of devouring...
[gasps]
...these carrots, which have devoured
all those animal nutrients,
must have been especially delicious.
[gasping]
Oh, my...
Speechless, are we?
[grunts, groans]
[groaning]
[yelps]
Surely, you don't have any intention
of criticizing me about this, Legoshi.
I've read all about you, my friend.
About how you willingly ate the flesh
and blood of your conscious classmate,
to somewhat ironically win a duel
against a devourer classmate.
- That's some determination.
- [groaning]
But can consider this
good conduct, I wonder?
[grunting]
What do you think, Gosha?
[grunts]
Do you understand what you're doing here?
No one is going to accept
a mammal and a reptile
starting a mixed blood family.
[groans] That may be.
But I also understand
that every family has its own troubles.
And whatever they are,
she and I will face them together!
There's a true happiness
that exists out there.
That's what I've been searching for
for my entire life!
I never imagined that someone
could love a venomous lizard.
Forgive me, my friend.
[Yahya] I'm afraid I can't do that, Gosha.
And now, the choice you made
out of a hunger for love,
had led to your dear grandchild
to the sole of my boot,
to be judged by my absolute authority.
[groaning]
Let me explain something to you.
Out here in the real world,
the first thing one must do
to escape a crisis,
is show absolute sincerity.
[stutters] Sincerity?
I want you to beg for my forgiveness.
Regardless of the reason,
a Beastar cannot excuse the devouring
of a living herbivore, you must realize.
However, if you're willing to grovel
here on the ground before me,
with a sincere apology to me for ever
being born a carnivore in the first place,
then at least you won't end up
as fertilizer,
like the many beasts who came before you.
Now, what do you say?
[Legoshi] I only did it because
I would've never beaten Riz otherwise.
But, an apology for being born
a carnivore?
[Yahya] Time to settle this, Gosha.
Which one of us is wrong?
And which is righteous?
For being born a carnivore,
and for eating my friend's leg...
I'm sorry.
Although I had consent,
I did something unforgivable.
- [squelching]
- [Legoshi groans]
I try to atone for it every day.
- [squelching]
- [pants, grunts]
I plan to live with what I've done.
[panting, grunting]
[slurring] And that's why...
[panting]
...from now on...
[tense music playing]
I don't need fangs!
- [fangs clatter]
- [breathing heavily]
[tense music crescendos]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my sid e ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪